https://www.indivaragroup.com/index.php/privacy-policy/

Nusantara Sejahtera Investama, PT
Seedbox Technologies, Inc.
Enabler Businesses
JATIS GROUP
NEWS & EVENTS
Ayala Corp one of the oldest and largest conglomerates in the Philippines tie-up with Indivara Group to give the Filipinos broaden Digital Experience
Indivara Group and Del Institute of Technology (IT Del) have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) for Youth Development
DMSM and MPM Finance Tie Up to Provide Financing for Moms and Pops Stores
Loket Pintar Indonesia, PT select Indivara Payment Platform to serve customers with better transaction experience
BTN upscale Their Online Wealth Management Services with Avantrade Investment Portal
Taspen Life selects Indivara payment platform to serve customers with better transaction experience
PNM Investment Management, PT goes digital with Avantrade Investment Portal
CAREER
Search for:
Nusantara Sejahtera Investama, PT
Seedbox Technologies, Inc.
Enabler Businesses
JATIS GROUP
NEWS & EVENTS
Ayala Corp one of the oldest and largest conglomerates in the Philippines tie-up with Indivara Group to give the Filipinos broaden Digital Experience
Indivara Group and Del Institute of Technology (IT Del) have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) for Youth Development
DMSM and MPM Finance Tie Up to Provide Financing for Moms and Pops Stores
Loket Pintar Indonesia, PT select Indivara Payment Platform to serve customers with better transaction experience
BTN upscale Their Online Wealth Management Services with Avantrade Investment Portal
Taspen Life selects Indivara payment platform to serve customers with better transaction experience
PNM Investment Management, PT goes digital with Avantrade Investment Portal
PT Dinamika Mitra Sukses Makmur
Seedbox Technologies, Inc.
This Privacy Statement is effective as of 31 March 2020.
At Indivara we recognize the importance of protecting your personal information and are committed to processing it responsibly and in compliance with applicable data protection laws in all countries in which Indivara operates.
This Privacy Statement describes Indivara’s general privacy practices that apply to personal information we collect, use and share about consumers and other individuals within our clients, business partners, supplier and other organizations with which Indivara has or contemplates a business relationship.
We may provide additional or more specific information on the collection or use of personal information on websites or related to a specific product or service.
Why and how we collect and use your personal information
We may collect your personal information as an individual for various purposes, such as the following:
Access and use of websites or other online services
When entering one of our websites, or using an online service, we will record information necessary to provide you with access, for the operation of the website and for us to comply with security and legal requirements in relation to operating our site, such as passwords, IP address and browser settings. We also collect information about your activities during your visit in order to personalize your website experience, such as recording your preferences and settings, and to collect statistics to help us improve and further develop our websites, platforms and services.
Responding to your request for information, order, or support
When you contact us (online or offline) in connection with a request for information, to order a platform or solutions, to provide you with support, or to participate in a forum or other social computing tool, we collect information necessary to fulfill your request, to grant you access to the service, to provide you with support and to be able to contact you. For instance, we collect your name and contact information, details about your request and your agreement with us and the fulfillment, delivery and invoicing of your order and we may include client satisfaction survey information. We retain such information for administrative purposes, defending our rights, and in connection with our relationship with you.
When you provide your name and contact information to register in connection with such a request, the registration may serve to identify you when you visit our websites.
Contacting employees of our clients, prospects, partners and suppliers
In our relationship with clients or prospects, partners and suppliers, they also provide us with business contact information (such as name, business contact details, position or title of their employees, contractors, advisors and authorized users) for purposes such as contract management, fulfillment, delivery of platforms and services, provision of support, invoicing and management of the services or the relationship.
Marketing
Most information we collect about you comes from our direct interactions with you. When you register for an event we may collect information (online or offline) in relation to the event organization, and during an event, such as participation in sessions and survey results. We combine the personal information we collect to develop aggregate analysis and business intelligence for conducting our business and for marketing purposes. You can choose to receive information by email, telephone or postal mail about our platforms and services, or sign-up for subscriptions. When visiting our websites or using our services we may provide you with personalized information. You can always opt-out from receiving personalized communication by sending an e-mail to info@indivaragroup.com .
Where we reference that we use your personal information in connection with a request, order, transaction or agreement (or preparing for the same), or to provide you with services that you requested (such as a website), we do this because it is necessary for the performance of an agreement with you.
Where we reference that we use your personal information in relation to marketing, improvement or development of our platforms or services, for reasons of safety and security, or regulatory requirements other than in connection with your agreement or request, we do this on the basis of our or a third party’s legitimate interests, or with your consent.
Sharing of Personal Information
As a regional organization offering a wide range of platforms and services, with business processes, management structures and technical systems that cross borders, Indivara has implemented global policies, along with standards and procedures, for consistent protection of personal information. As a regional company, we may share information about you with our subsidiaries and transfer it to countries in the region where we do business in accordance with this Privacy Statement.
Between Indivara controlled subsidiaries we only grant access to personal information on a need-to-know basis, necessary for the purposes for which such access is granted. In some cases, Indivara uses suppliers located in various countries to collect, use, analyze, and otherwise process personal information on its behalf.
Where appropriate, Indivara may also share your personal information with selected partners to help us provide you, or the company you work for, platforms or services, or to fulfill your requests, or with your consent. When selecting our suppliers and partners, we take into account their data handling processes.
If Indivara decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries, such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of such information from sellers. It is Indivara’s practice to require appropriate protection for personal information in these types of transactions.
Please be aware that in certain circumstances, personal information may be subject to disclosure to government agencies pursuant to judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. We may also share your personal information to protect the rights or property of Indivara, our business partners, suppliers or clients, and others when we have reasonable grounds to believe that such rights or property have been or could be affected.
Information Security and Accuracy
We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its accuracy. Indivara implements reasonable physical, administrative and technical safeguards to help us protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure. For example, we encrypt certain sensitive personal information such as credit card information when we transmit such information over the Internet. We also require that our suppliers protect such information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure.
Retention Period
We will not retain personal information longer than necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is processed, including the security of our processing complying with legal and regulatory obligations (e.g. audit, accounting and statutory retention terms), handling disputes, and for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims in the countries where we do business.
How to contact us
If you have a question related to this Privacy Statement, please contact us by sending us an email to info@indivaragroup.com . Your message will be forwarded to the appropriate member of Indivara’s Data Privacy Team, such as Data Protection Officers or members of their teams.
Indivara Group is not the controller in situations such as:
Personal information processed in connection with a contractual relationship, or with entering into a contractual relationship with a specific Indivara subsidiary. In this case the controller of personal information is the Indivara contracting company, which is the legal entity with which you or your employer have, or will have, the contract.
Personal information collected on the physical site or location of an Indivara subsidiary. In this case that subsidiary is the controller of the personal information.
Your Rights
You can request to access, update, delete or correct your personal information. You also have the right to object to direct marketing. You can send the request process by sending us an email to info@indivaragroup.com .
Right to Lodge a Complaint
In the event you consider our processing of your personal information not to be compliant with the applicable data protection laws, you can lodge a complaint:
Directly with Indivara by sending us an email to : info@indivaragroup.com
Changes to our Privacy Statements
We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time to reflect changes to our data governance practices. The revised Privacy Statement will be posted here with an updated revision date. We encourage you to check back periodically for any changes or updates. If we make a material change to our Privacy Statement, we will post a notice at the top of this page for 30 days. By continuing to use our websites after such revision takes effect we consider that you have read and understand the changes.
PRODUCTSAVANTRADE Wealth Management System
PAYMENT
SAPPHIRE
ETALAZE
HCMS
IRIS ENTERPRISE SUPPORT PLATFORM
INDIGO! Corporate Travel Management
About Us Indivara Group is one of the largest technology investment holding company in ASEAN which focuses on consulting/software development and platform businesses.
Contact Us PT. INDIVARA SEJAHTERA SUKSES MAKMUR.
2020 Indivara. All rights reserved.
